all right thanks everyone for coming
好的，谢谢大家的光临
I'm Eric and today we're gonna talk a
我是埃里克，今天我们要谈一个
bit about the g1 garbage collector in
关于g1垃圾收集器的一点
JDK 9 but before we begin I would just
JDK 9，但在我们开始之前，我只是
like to show you all this slide let it
想给你看这张幻灯片
hang out there for a few over seconds
在那里闲逛几秒钟
for you to enjoy and now that's out of
让您享受，现在已经不在了
the way let's look at today's agenda
让我们看看今天的议程的方式
we're gonna be talking about the g1
我们要谈论的是g1
garbage collector and first of all we're
垃圾收集器，首先我们是
gonna start off with a quick intro into
从快速介绍开始
g1 in 2017 we will then continue on
在2017年的g1上，我们将继续
looking at five major improvements to g1
研究g1的五个主要改进
since JDK 8 and then last but not least
从JDK 8开始，最后但并非最不重要
we will do a little bit of sneak peek
我们会偷看一下
into the future and see what's coming up
进入未来，看看会发生什么
for d1 but who am i I'm Eric I like to
对于d1，但我是谁我是Eric我想
program garbage collectors I work at
我工作的程序垃圾收集器
Oracle in the JVM GC team and has done
Oracle在JVM GC团队中已经做到
so for about six years now the past
所以过去大约六年
three years I've worked on the g1
我在g1上工作了三年
garbage collector and I was a reviewer
垃圾收集器，我是评论员
and open in decay where I contributed a
并在衰落中开放，我贡献了
lot so the quick intro into g1 in 2017
很多，所以在2017年快速介绍了g1
first of all what is garbage collector
首先是什么垃圾收集器
and what is g1 solving well garbage
什么是g1很好解决垃圾
collection is a way to manage memory
收集是管理内存的一种方式
so in Java programmers do not need to
因此在Java中，程序员不需要
explicitly manage to memory ourselves
明确地去记忆自己
you will allocate your objects with new
您将为您的对象分配新的
and then the memory will be reclaimed by
然后内存将被回收
the garbage collector once it's no
垃圾收集器一旦没有
longer in use you can compare this to
使用时间更长，您可以将其与
see where programs programmers must
看看程序程序员必须在哪里
manage the memory themselves using
自己使用管理内存
malloc and free how the Scourge
malloc和如何释放天灾
collection work well all your objects
集合可以很好地处理所有对象
will be allocated in a memory area
将分配在内存区域
called the heap these objects will be
这些对象称为堆
laid out in memory with respective
分别与
fields those fields can in turn contain
这些字段可以包含的字段
references to other objects but also in
对其他对象的引用
google internal values as you allocate
谷歌内部价值分配
more and more objects you will start to
您将开始越来越多的对象
fill up this memory area called heap and
填满这个称为堆的内存区域，
once it's completely filled up well
一旦完全填满
there's no space to allocate more
没有空间分配更多
obviously and so something as gonna have
显然，诸如此类的东西
to happen now if the program is gonna
如果该程序要现在发生
continue running what it's going to
继续运行它将要做什么
happen is that the garbage collector
碰巧是垃圾收集器
will force your application and then it
将强制您的应用程序，然后
will
将
see which objects are currently in use
查看当前正在使用哪些对象
by the program because if you think
通过该程序，因为如果您认为
about when you write that method in Java
关于何时用Java编写该方法
you might allocate a bunch of objects do
你可能会分配一堆对象
some computation and then return the
一些计算，然后返回
result but those objects you use for a
结果，但您用于
competition you don't really need them
比赛你真的不需要他们
anymore
不再
so the garbage doctor will find out
所以垃圾医生会找出来
which objects are in use and will do so
哪些对象正在使用中，并将这样做
by starting from the so-called routes so
从所谓的路线开始
in order to figure out which objects are
为了找出哪些对象是
live and heap and being in used by the
生活和堆放，并被
programs you stopped in your application
您在应用程序中停止的程序
you scan the Fred stacks for the Java
您扫描Fred堆栈中的Java
threads you find the references pointing
您找到引用指向的线程
out objects like this and then you say
拿出这样的物体，然后你说
that now I've found those objects I'm
现在我找到了那些我
gonna consider them live but as you see
会认为他们活着，但正如你所见
on the slide we're just a bunch more
在幻灯片上，我们只是更多
objects and we can iterate over the
对象，我们可以遍历
fields in each object in turn and follow
每个对象中的字段依次
of the references and then we will find
参考，然后我们会发现
more objects that are reachable from the
从中可以访问的更多对象
roots and if you keep doing this an
根，如果您继续这样做
iterate on this algorithm we will
迭代此算法，我们将
simulate or find them all once we have
一旦有，就模拟或找到它们
found those objects we can compact them
找到了那些我们可以压实的物体
to one end of the heap there are other
到堆的一端
schemes available from memory management
内存管理中可用的方案
but this is one example the objects can
但这是对象可以
be compacted to one another heap and we
被压紧到另一个堆，我们
will have now have a continuous free
现在将有连续的免费
memory area we can use for new
我们可以用于新的存储区
allocations the program can then resume
程序可以重新分配
running and suddenly there's more space
跑步，突然有更多空间
for new objects to be allocated in
用于在其中分配新对象
jae-won is one such garbage collection
Jae-won就是这样的垃圾收集器之一
algorithm and this is the first page of
算法，这是第一页
the original paper which is getting a
原始纸正在
little bit old by now so the paper was
现在有点老了，所以纸是
published in 2004 on g1 garbage
2004年发表在g1垃圾上
collector the JDK got experimental
JDK的收藏家进行了实验
support for day 1 in 6 to 14 and
支持6至14天的第一天
official support in JDK 7 u 4 in 2012
2012年JDK 7 u 4中的官方支持
and this year a few weeks ago when JDK 9
而今年几周前，当JDK 9
was released q1 became the default
已发布q1成为默认值
collector for the JDK so with this
JDK的收集器，因此
information
信息
be wary when you're reading old blog
阅读旧博客时要小心
posts Stack Overflow answers etc about G
发布有关G的堆栈溢出答案等
1 because quite a bit has changed
1，因为发生了很大的变化
between 2009 and 2017 the G 1 has
在2009年至2017年之间，G 1
evolved a lot since it was first
自诞生以来就发展了很多
introduced with experimental support
在实验支持下引入
so the goal of g1 is to provide both
所以g1的目标是
throughput and low latency and
吞吐量和低延迟
throughput you can think of that as
吞吐量，您可以将其视为
roughly the number of transactions per
大致每笔交易的数量
second or the total running time of a
秒或总的运行时间
program whereas latency that will more
程序，而延迟会更多
correspond to the maximum time of a
对应于一个的最大时间
transaction and the default post call
交易和默认邮寄电话
for g1 is 200 milliseconds this post
g1的发布时间为200毫秒
goal can be tuned you can say to g1 I'm
目标可以调整，你可以对g1说我
ok with longer pauses which probably
还可以停顿更长的时间
will result if you have a back-end
如果有后端，将会出现
service for example in longer request
服务，例如更长的请求
times but in turn you will get better
时代，但反过来你会变得更好
throughput and get more work done per
吞吐量并完成更多工作
time unit whereas if you are concerned
时间单位，而如果您担心
about latency and say that I don't want
关于延迟，并说我不想
it to post not at all or very little you
它根本不发布或很少发布
can decrease this value to a much lower
可以将此值降低到更低
value but there's always a trade-off so
价值，但总会有一个权衡取舍
here you're gonna have to sacrifice
在这里，你将不得不牺牲
throughput a bit but in turn you will
一点点的吞吐量，但是您将
get shorter forces so how does do you
得到较短的力量，那你怎么办
wanna achieve this well the goal here is
想达到这个目标的目的是
where the methyl here is to use
在这里使用甲基
generational region based memory
基于世代区域的记忆
management
管理
that's quite a term so the heap is split
这是一个术语，所以堆被拆分了
into multiple regions so the region size
分成多个区域，因此区域大小
will depend on the heap size for example
例如，将取决于堆大小
if you have 4 gigabyte heap then you g1
如果您有4 GB的堆，则g1
will divide it into 2048 2 megabyte
将其分为2048 2兆字节
regions new objects are allocated into
新对象分配到的区域
so-called Eden regions and a John
所谓的伊甸园地区和约翰
collection will happen after a number of
收集将在多个
Eden regions have been allocated during
伊甸园地区已在
such a young collection j-1 will find
j-1这样年轻的收藏家会发现
live objects in those Eden regions and
在那些伊甸园地区的活物和
compactly copy them into a survival
紧凑地复制它们以生存
region objects will then continue to be
然后，区域对象将继续是
allocated in Eden regions and after a
在伊甸园地区分配
while if an object survives multiple
而如果一个对象可以存活多个
John collections they are compactly
约翰收集他们紧凑
copied into an old region so as your
复制到旧的区域，例如
program keeps running more and more
程序不断运行
intermediates will be used for
中间体将用于
allocations young collections will
青年收藏品的分配将
happens the objects will be surviving
碰巧物体会幸存
and moving into survival regions some
并进入一些生存地区
ways survive for longer times filling up
方式可以存活更长的时间
more and more old regions with live
越来越多的地区与生活
objects and sooner rather than later g1
对象，而不是迟于g1
will have to start a concurrent mark
将必须开始一个并发标记
cycle to find out in the old regions
循环寻找旧地区
which objects are actually in use in
实际使用哪些对象
which or n't so the job application is
求职申请是哪个
not stopped during this time the
在这段时间内没有停止
concurrent mark will be running
并发标记将运行
alongside your job application
连同您的工作申请
traversing the heap and finding all
遍历堆并找到所有
these live objects in the old regions
这些古老地区的生物
then once the concurrent marking cycle
然后一次并发标记周期
is finished even survive an old regions
完成，甚至可以在一个古老的地区生存
or collected in so called mixed
或收集在所谓的混合
collections the live objects are again
再次收集活动对象
compactly copied into survivor and old
紧凑地复制到幸存者和老
radians so on the side here in this
弧度，所以在这边
example we are taking all of the Eden
例子，我们把所有的伊甸园
and survival regions which must be
和生存区域必须
collected every time and also shows in
每次都收集并在
two old regions to collect the result is
两个老地区收集的结果是
time goes on G when we collect more and
当我们收集更多的东西时，时间在G
more of the old regions so more and more
越来越多的旧地区
of the heap will become free and then
的堆将变为空闲，然后
once they're no longer or an old
一旦他们不再是老了
gradients suitable for collection for
适合收集的渐变
example they might contain too many live
例如，它们可能包含太多直播
objects too is not worth collecting them
物品也不值得收集
jibon will once again resume doing junk
吉邦将再次恢复做垃圾
collections thus g1 moves and
因此，集合g1移动并
transitions between the following states
以下状态之间的转换
it starts out by doing young collections
它从做年轻的收藏开始
which will copy objects into survivor
将对象复制到幸存者中
regions and promote them to old regions
地区并将其推广到旧地区
after a while as the heap is getting
过了一会儿，就像堆越来越
more and more full a concurrent mark
越来越多的并发标记
cycle will be started the concurrent
周期将开始并发
mark Sotka is not only running
马克·索特卡（Sotka）不仅在跑
concurrently with your application they
与您的应用程序同时进行
can also happens young collections
也会发生年轻的收藏
during the concurrent mark circles
在并发标记圈中
running once the hard mark finishes g1
一旦硬标记完成就运行g1
transitions are going to do with mixed
过渡与混合有关
collections and once they are no longer
收藏，一旦它们不再
and in suitable regions to collect it
并在合适的地方收集
once again transition back to do enjoin
再次过渡回去做命令
collections and so the cycle repeats
集合，所以循环重复
so we wrapped a bit of knowledge about
所以我们包装了一些关于
how g1 works we're going to look at five
g1的工作方式我们将看五个
major improvements and how they were
重大改进及其进展
done that has happened since the JDK 8
自JDK 8以来所做的事情
so we're gonna have a look at string the
所以我们来看看字符串
application introduced in 8020 we're
在8020年推出的应用程序
gonna see cloth unloading with
会看到布卸下
concurrent marks with shipped in a 2-14
并发标记与2-14
we're gonna see the eagerly reclamation
我们将看到热切的填海
of humongous regions introduced in 8 to
在8个地区引入的庞大地区
and then the adaptive sort of the
然后是适应性的
co-current mark cycle this is shipped in
并发标记周期
Yeti not just recently and also about
雪人不仅是最近，而且也是
with a lot more efficient collections
收集效率更高
that were also shipped in Yeti canine
也被运送到雪人犬身上
but let's start out with string the
但让我们从字符串开始
application so in this example we are
应用程序，因此在此示例中
allocating two strings I have one named
分配两个字符串，我有一个命名
conf one and j1 j1 we often put your 1
conf one和j1 j1我们经常把你的1
and they have very similar content if
他们的内容非常相似，如果
you look at the slide they actually are
你看他们实际上是的幻灯片
identical and now you might now think a
相同，现在您可能会认为
little bit couldn't we make better use
一点我们不能更好地利用
of the memory instead of having this
而不是拥有
duplicated character arrays on the heap
堆上重复的字符数组
taking up valuable space could we do
占用宝贵的空间我们可以做
this would that be okay or could it be
那样可以吗？
any problems with the java program if we
Java程序的任何问题，如果我们
were to do this little trick it is
要做这个小技巧
actually perfectly legal and valid and
实际上完全合法有效
fine
精细
because in Java like string the
因为在Java中，像字符串
character array value is both private
字符数组的值都是私有的
and final so if we do this behind the
最后，如果我们在
scenes that your Java program will not
Java程序不会看到的场景
notice any difference the way we do this
注意我们执行此方法的任何不同
is that during a collection g1 adds all
是在收集期间g1将所有
new newly allocated strings to a queue
新分配的新字符串到队列
and then after the young collection is
然后年轻的收藏是
done g1 will concurrently check if any
完成g1将同时检查是否有
two strings equals if the two strings
两个字符串等于两个字符串是否相等
are identical then you can make them
一样，那么你可以让他们
refer I will give one mixed and refer to
我会给一个混合并参考
the same character array and please note
相同的字符数组，请注意
this is not the same thing as in turn
这与反过来是不一样的
strings string in turn cares about
依次关心的字符串
string objects whereas during the
字符串对象，而在
application cares about the character
应用程序关心字符
arrays or the value fields and
数组或值字段以及
internally in the AVM they use different
在AVM内部，他们使用不同的
tables this can save a lot of memory and
表可以节省大量内存，并且
a lot of footprint on the heap depending
堆上的很多足迹取决于
on your application of course if you
当然在您的申请中
have a lot of maybe a lot of SQL
有很多也许很多SQL
statements that are repeated or a very
重复或非常重复的陈述
that contains the same values this can
包含相同的值
be a big memory saver the trade of this
成为一个大的内存保护程序
that it will use slightly more CPU due
由于它将使用更多的CPU
to the concurrent work going on at the
到正在进行的并发工作
same time and it might also cost
同时，这可能也会花费
slightly just a bit longer John
约翰稍长一点
collections so if it works it worth it
收藏，所以如果它值得，那就值得
or not that depends on your application
是否取决于您的应用
how much memory is save and your CPU
节省多少内存和您的CPU
requirements you can try this out with
要求，您可以尝试一下
use students application in Yeti k8u 20
在Yeti k8u 20中使用学生应用程序
and later the next improvement we're
然后下一个改进是
gonna look at this class unloading with
去看这个课
concurrent mark and this is a tricky
并发标记，这很棘手
subject so objects on the heap have a
主题，因此堆上的对象具有
corresponding class and those classes
对应的班级和那些班级
have in turn being loaded by a class
依次由一个类加载
loader when the objects are when all
加载器何时所有对象
instances of a class on the heap are
堆上一个类的实例是
dead that means that the class itself is
死了，这意味着该类本身是
dead and of if all closest loaded by the
已死，如果所有最近的都由
same class loader are dead that means
同一类加载器已死，这意味着
that we can unload these classes and
我们可以卸载这些类并
garbage collect the corresponding class
垃圾收集对应的类
loader now the question is how do we
装载机现在的问题是我们如何
find out if a class is dead or not
找出班级是否已经死亡
well j1 will traverse the entire heap
j1将遍历整个堆
and as it does so finding live objects
并因此找到活动对象
it will encounter live objects and can
它将遇到有生命的物体，并且可以
therefore from those novel objects find
因此从那些新颖的物体中找到
out which class they belong to or in
他们属于哪一类
Orion sources of and mark the
Orion的来源并标记
corresponding class as live since a
自从
clause can only be unloaded if all
子句只能在所有
classes loaded by that Clause cross
该子句加载的类交叉
loader are dead we will mark the closed
装载机已死，我们将标记为已关闭
address live and all classes loaded by
处理实时和加载的所有类
the class loader as live as d1 traverses
与d1遍历一样的类加载器
the heap more and finds more and more
堆越来越多，发现越来越多
live objects more and more classes will
活物会越来越多
be marked as live and the corresponding
被标记为直播，相应的
class loaders after the heap has been
堆之后的类加载器
hit rate a few when we found all live
当我们发现所有直播时的点击率
objects we can in turn iterate through
我们可以依次遍历的对象
the class loader graph and find out
类加载器图并找出
there's an openness a class though there
虽然那里有一个开放的课堂
isn't work that's live that means that
没有工作就是活着，这意味着
closed or is dead
关闭或已死
and we can unload all the classes that
我们可以卸载所有的类
class loader has loaded so in one tricky
类加载器已加载，因此棘手
sentence after all objects have been
所有对象都经过后的句子
visited then unload all classes loaded
访问然后卸载所有已加载的类
by class loaders that aren't live and
按类别分类的非现场装载机
there are two algorithms in g1 that
在g1中有两种算法
visits all live objects on the heap
访问堆上的所有活动对象
you have the concurrent marking which is
你有并发标记是
it's really tricky to to find out the
找出
live losses during current marking but
当前标记期间的实时损失，但
it performs pretty well and then we also
它表现很好，然后我们也
the fall back full garbage collection
退回完整垃圾回收
here is a lot easier to find out which
这很容易找出
which classes are live
哪些课程是直播的
it's slow and will cause longer pauses
它很慢，会导致更长的暂停
so in JDK a 240 we finally shipped close
所以在JDK 240中，我们终于发货了
unloading after concurrent marking this
并发标记后卸载
is controlled by the flag cloth
由旗布控制
unloading with concurrent mark and it's
卸载并发标记，它是
enabled by default since 1840 and it can
自1840年起默认启用，它可以
reduce the need for full full back full
减少全额补足的需要
DC's quite a lot in your application if
如果您的应用中有很多DC，
you load and unload a lot of classes and
您加载和卸载了很多类，
again available in a t14 later the next
再次在t14中可用，下一个
little trick or improvement or feature
小技巧或改进或功能
be done is well be done money but one
做好是钱，但是一个
significant is equally reclamation or
重要的是同等的填海或
igloo reclaim of humongous regions and
圆顶冰屋回收大片地区和
this was shipped in 1860 so let's have a
这是在1860年发货的，所以让我们
look at that one when objects are larger
当物体更大时，看着那个
than half a region they are called
他们被称为一半以上的地区
humongous in g1 and the region's they
在g1和该地区的巨大
are allocated in or called humongous
被分配或称为巨大
regions g1 doesn't copy humongous
区域g1不复制巨大
objects around on heap because it's too
因为它也是对象
expensive they are large and half a
昂贵，他们是大半
region so they take up a lot of memory
区域，因此占用大量内存
so thereby copying them takes a lot of
因此复制它们需要很多
time something we do not want to do but
时间我们不想做但
on the other hand these objects use a
另一方面，这些对象使用
lot of memory and if they become dead we
很多记忆，如果它们死了，我们
want to free that up pretty quickly so
想要很快释放它，所以
we can reuse it for other objects and
我们可以将其重用于其他对象
allocations so what we do is that we
分配，所以我们要做的是
utilize the fact that g1 keeps track of
利用g1跟踪的事实
references between old regions as can be
可以在旧区域之间引用
seen on a slide here we have a couple of
在幻灯片上可以看到，我们有几个
old radius regions and one humongous
古老的半径地区和一个巨大的地方
region we see that there are no incoming
区域，我们看到没有传入
references to that one humongous object
提到那个巨大的物体
in the humongous region and there is one
在这个庞大的地区，有一个
outgoing references from a humongous
巨大的传出引用
object but since there are no incoming
对象，但由于没有传入
references from other objects in old
来自其他旧对象的引用
gradients that means that the only thing
渐变，这意味着唯一
that can keep this humongous object
可以保留这个巨大的物体
alive is an object in a John region that
活着是约翰地区的一个物体
is either in a region or survival region
在一个地区或生存地区
but remember when we do a giant
但要记得当我们做一个巨人
collection we will look at all the live
收藏品，我们将现场直播
objects in all the John regions so
所有约翰地区的对象
during the junk collection g1 will check
在垃圾收集期间，g1会检查
if drawer and references from a John
如果抽屉和约翰的参考
Young object to this humongous object if
年轻的人反对这个庞大的对象，如果
no references are found from John
找不到约翰的参考
obvious we know that nothing is holding
很明显，我们知道什么都没有
on to this human
对这个人
we can reclaim the memory and reuse it
我们可以回收内存并重复使用
later so day 1 can do to this feature
之后，第1天可以使用此功能
reclaim him along with objects during a
在一个
young collection it does not need to
年轻的收藏，它不需要
wait for concurrent mark to finish to
等待并发标记完成
realize that object is dead this was
意识到物体已经死了
introduced in 1860 and can help quell
于1860年推出，可以帮助平息
loss if you have if you allocate a large
如果您分配了一大笔钱，就会亏损
objects so the next feature gonna look
对象，所以下一个功能会看起来
at is the adaptive sort of concurrent
at是自适应的并发类型
mark and this was shipped in JDK 9 so
标记，这是在JDK 9中交付的，因此
this concurrent mark cycle that looks
看起来并发的标记周期
through all the live objects in all the
通过所有
old regions again it can take a little
再次需要一些旧区域
bit of time until it finishes but it's
一点时间直到完成，但是
important that it does finish because if
它确实完成很重要，因为如果
it doesn't finish then g1 doesn't have
它没有完成，然后g1没有
the liveness information needed to
需要的活动信息
collect objects in the old region's so
收集旧地区的物体
co-current marking must finish before
并流标记必须在之前完成
the heap is full with old regions and
堆满了旧的地区和
the problem is done of course when
问题当然是解决了
should have distorted prior to yet ek9
在ek9之前应该已经变形了
you had to use the flag initiating heap
您必须使用标志启动堆
or kc % which meant that you set a value
或kc％，表示您设置了一个值
for example 35 and concurrent marking
例如35和并发标记
would be started when the heap was 35%
将在堆为35％时启动
full now this is obviously a way to
现在满了，这显然是一种方法
static way to do this and many of you
静态方式来做到这一点
experience problems with this that the
遇到这个问题
concurrent mark saga was kicked off too
并发标记传奇也开始了
early resulting a slightly worse
早期导致稍差
performance or too late resulting at we
性能或为时已晚
couldn't collect old regions so in 9 we
无法收集旧区域，所以在9中
replace this with a much more adaptive
用更具适应性的替换它
dynamic calculation we do use for the
我们确实将动态计算用于
first collections just as an initial
最初的收藏
value to the ergonomics engine the value
对人体工程学引擎的价值
of this flag and then we sample runtime
该标志的然后我们对运行时进行采样
data and see how the applications
数据并查看应用程序
allocation performs and how much data
分配执行以及多少数据
you allocate and then we can use those
您分配，然后我们可以使用那些
samples and the feedback from previous
样本和以前的反馈
concurrent mark cycles to determine when
并发标记周期以确定何时
to start off the next one and of course
开始下一个，当然
we always had a safety margin because we
我们总是有安全余量，因为我们
really wanted to finish in time so this
我真的很想及时完成，所以这
results in much less concurrent mark
导致更少的并发标记
failures which in turn saves you from a
失败反过来使您免于
lot of this fall back full GCS
大部分回退到完整的GCS
this is controlled with a flag - xxg one
这由一个标志控制-xxg一个
use adaptive I hope and this is enabled
我希望使用自适应，并且已启用
by default in 89 and I recommend you to
默认情况下是89，我建议您
keep it on so let's look a bit at the
保持打开状态，让我们看一下
new more efficient collections that we
我们新的更有效的收藏
have introduced in JDK 9 we did a lot of
在JDK 9中已经介绍过，我们做了很多
work going into UDK 9 in fact we had
实际上进入UDK 9的工作
more than 250 announcements going in for
超过250条公告
G 1 there are things all over the place
G 1到处都是东西
there are more parallel phase sisters
有更多的平行相姐妹
improved peel up sizing parallel freeing
改善剥离尺寸平行释放
we have T lab resizing concurrent mark
我们有T实验室调整并发标记的大小
from rules and a bunch more updates to
从规则和更多更新
the internal data structures for the
内部数据结构
garbage collector we have more than 180
垃圾收集器，我们有180多个
bug fixes going into G 1 G C in your
您的G 1 GC中的错误修复
canine so what is the effect of all this
犬，这一切的作用是什么
well how much did we actually improve
我们实际上有多少改进
well the uptake has actually been great
嗯，实际上吸收量很大
here I have a bunch of nice logos and
在这里，我有一堆漂亮的徽标，
code some various things and then I pipe
编写一些各种各样的东西，然后我用管道
the slides for legal and out came this
合法的幻灯片出来了
slide so J 1 has been picked up by major
幻灯片，因此J 1已被少校拾取
Java frameworks and applications
Java框架和应用程序
especially Google applications such as
特别是Google应用程序，例如
some very well-known IDs and also
一些非常知名的ID
server-side frameworks so many major
服务器端框架如此之多
companies have also switched or or
公司也已切换或
switching to g1 for the workloads
切换到g1进行工作负载
particularly those where they care about
特别是那些他们关心的人
the post times but also cares about the
发布时间，但也关心
throughput need a mix of those and
吞吐量需要混合使用
remember to always run with latest JDK
切记始终与最新的JDK一起运行
release if you are running with D 1
如果使用D 1运行则释放
because the improvements are kept being
因为不断改进
kept added so you want to ensure to get
保持添加状态，以便您确保获得
the best performance that you are
最好的表现
running with the latest version so let's
以最新版本运行，让我们
look a little bit in to the future of g1
展望g1的未来
and what is it going on at the moment we
这是怎么回事
are not I live sitting by we are
我不是坐在我们旁边吗
continuing improving and developing even
持续改善甚至发展
though 9 is just released so for the
尽管9刚刚发布，所以对于
next year DK release we are looking
我们期待明年的DK版本
forward to parallel fall back full DC so
前向并行后退全DC，因此
the reason that all of you have cell
你们所有人都有细胞的原因
problems will fall back which is the
问题将回退，这是
full UC is not supposed to happen which
完全的UC应该不会发生
a one but if it does happen it has
一个，但是如果确实发生了
really painful in the post so for the
在帖子中真的很痛苦，所以对于
next decade release we are looking
我们期待的下一个十年版本
forward to parallel fold back full uses
正向平行折回充分利用
that even though it is a failure case
即使是失败案例
you will have a much faster and speedy
您将拥有更快，更快的速度
recovery
复苏
this is being reviewed right now on the
现在正在对此进行审查
mailing lists and you can see more
邮件列表，您可以看到更多
details in Jeff 307 on open a decay that
Jeff 307中的细节打开了一个衰减
your nuts that kept slash 307 we have
你的坚果一直斜线307
also made significant improvements to
也对
the core scanning so of course then it
核心扫描当然是
scanning is a detail of how g1 works and
扫描是g1工作原理的详细信息，
it needs to perform quite a lot of it so
它需要执行很多工作，所以
this summer we revamped the code and
今年夏天，我们修改了代码，
improved it quite a bit which resolved
改善了很多，解决了
in a nice boost and shorter poses but we
以很好的提升和较短的姿势，但我们
do not stop there we are continuing to
不要停在那里，我们继续
push even further continuously and at
持续不断地推动
the moment there are patches going on to
当有补丁继续进行时
rebuild the remember sets concurrently
同时重建记忆集
we haven't looked into those today but
我们今天没有调查
remember sister our key data structure
记得姐姐我们的关键数据结构
into how g1 works and in the future we
讨论g1的工作原理，并在将来
can hopefully rebuild them concurrently
希望可以同时重建它们
we are also doing a lot of work into the
我们还在做很多工作
ergonomics engine trying to improve it
人体工程学引擎试图对其进行改进
and improve your economic so you don't
并改善您的经济状况
have to tune as much but is that g1 can
必须尽可能多地调音，但是g1可以
itself figure out what values to use and
自己找出要使用的值，
what flags to set now if you will want
如果需要，现在设置什么标志
to stay connected and I hope you will
保持联系，希望您会
please join the community hotspot - TC -
请加入社区热点-TC-
use at open indicator java.net there are
使用在开放指示器java.net上有
a lot of experienced users on that pain
很多经验丰富的用户都在经历这种痛苦
list including the GC developers and to
列表，包括GC开发人员和
all you users who are on there helping
您在那里的所有用户都在提供帮助
each other thank you we really
互相谢谢你，我们真的
appreciate that you knew the ones who
感谢您认识那些谁
tuned a lot and have a lot of experience
调音很多，有很多经验
helped out the newcomers to the
帮助新来的人
community and as a questions we the GC
社区，还有一个问题，我们GC
developers also read this mailing list
开发人员还阅读了此邮件列表
but unfortunately we don't always have
但不幸的是我们并不总是有
time to answers so again thank you for
是时候回答了，再次感谢您
your Co providing answers you can also
您的公司提供答案，您也可以
find us using I am on OpenJDK channel on
使用我在OpenJDK频道上找到我们
IRC top c.net
IRC top c.net
we can chat with us if you have any
如果有的话我们可以和我们聊天
questions we are usually around and
我们通常会遇到的问题和
lastly but not least you can find me and
最后但并非最不重要的是，您可以找到我，
several others of the JDK and JVM devil
JDK和JVM魔鬼的其他几个
in the DevOps corner in the Oracle
在Oracle的DevOps角落
developer long share in Moscone West you
开发人员长期在Moscone West分享您
can learn more about working in 2g one
可以了解更多有关在2g中工作的信息
at open indicator java.net and learn
在开放指标java.net并学习
more about worker and java at work on
有关工作人员和Java的更多信息
java if you're on twitter please follow
Java，如果您在Twitter上，请关注
at OpenJDK over at worker and the
在OpenJDK，在worker和
hashtags java one and DevOps and with
主题标签Java one和DevOps以及
that I would like to leave say thank you
我想离开说谢谢
and the jumpy of time to questions so
和时间跳动的问题，所以
yeah question
是的问题
no I the question is I'm gonna repeat it
不，我的问题是我要重复一遍
for the video and they do I have any
视频，他们有吗
performance numbers that I can share
我可以分享的绩效数字
with you or benchmarks result and no I
与您或基准测试结果有关，不，我
don't have anyone I can share with you
没有可以与您分享的人
one slice today unfortunately but please
不幸的是今天一片
try it out and see how it performs I
试试看，看看它的表现如何
think you will be hopefully satisfied
想你会很满意
yeah question
是的问题
the story come again please yeah so the
故事又来了，是的，所以
question is how big are those regions a
问题是这些地区有多大？
region can be anywhere from one megabyte
区域可以从1兆字节开始
to 32 megabytes it depends on the you
到32兆字节取决于您
can set that yourself with - x6 g1 he
可以设置自己-x6 g1 he
produces but I would probably recommend
生产，但我可能会建议
that you leave do you want to select
你离开的你想选择吗
appropriate so I have the region it will
合适的，所以我有区域
look at the heap size in total and then
看一下堆的总大小，然后
decide but if you are having problems
决定但是如果您有问题
with for example humongous allocations
例如巨大的分配
and humongous objects then you might
和巨大的物体，那么你可能
want to bump it up a bit
想把它撞起来
yeah question again over here
是的，在这里再次提问
yeah so the question is if an object is
是的，所以问题是一个物体是否
bigger than reading size I said that the
大于阅读尺寸，我说
readings might be as small as one
读数可能只有一个
megabyte what if you allocate for
兆字节（如果分配）
example one and a half megabyte byte
示例一个半兆字节的字节
array for some R no image data or
一些R的数组没有图像数据或
something
某事
well when G 1 allocates then a humongous
当G 1分配好时，
region and a humongous region can span
区域和大型区域可以跨越
multiple regions so the object will be
多个区域，因此对象将是
consecutively laid out in multiple human
连续布置在多个人中
resilience in this case too if you have
在这种情况下，如果您有弹性
a 1/2 megabyte allocation and 1 megabyte
1/2兆字节的分配和1兆字节的分配
regions but it would still be the only
地区，但仍然是唯一的
object in those two regions which will
在这两个区域中的对象
be next to each other yeah question in
在彼此旁边是的问题
the back
背部
so the question is is this features to
所以问题是这个功能
eat application that was released in
吃在发布的应用程序
8020 on by default now it is not on by
默认情况下8020处于打开状态
default since there is a little cost in
默认，因为其中花费很少
terms of CPU both will concurrent work
CPU方面都可以并发工作
and but and also will work you in a pose
而且，也可以帮你摆个姿势
we have it off by default so you can opt
我们默认情况下将其关闭，因此您可以选择
into it yeah question the front
是的，对前面的问题
so the question is yeah I get the
所以问题是，我明白了
questions so if the question the
问题，如果问题
question is if an object is copied from
问题是是否从复制对象
one region to another region how do we
一个地区到另一个地区，我们如何
make sure that no Java threads or your
确保没有Java线程或您的
program is modifying to obey at the same
程序正在修改以同时服从
time the application is stopped the JVM
应用程序停止JVM的时间
can stop the java application which you
可以停止您所使用的Java应用程序
will not know this besides gee suppose
除了gee应该不会知道
in the log but the application is
在日志中，但应用程序是
stopped - no no work for your
停止了-没有您的工作
application is ongoing at the same time
申请同时进行
as the object is copied yeah question
作为对象被复制是的问题
air filter so the question is for
空气滤清器，所以问题是
adjunct collections are there any
有附属收藏吗
options similar to concurrent marking do
与并发标记相似的选项
you mean for example two concurrently
你的意思是例如两个并发
find the live objects engine witness
查找活动对象引擎见证
yeah so the candy one concurrently find
是的，所以糖果同时找到
it like objects in journal regions no it
就像期刊区域中的对象一样
can't it will stop the world but this is
不能阻止世界，但这是
based on the hypothesis which is very
基于非常大的假设
very often true that for Java most
通常对于大多数Java来说都是如此
objects are allocated either died young
对象分配要么死亡，要么年轻
or they live for a very long time so
或者他们活了很长时间
even though you will fill up the evil
即使你会填满邪恶
eden regions with quite a few objects
伊甸园地区有很多物体
when we stop we only have to care about
当我们停下来时，我们只需要关心
live objects and those are usually much
活物，通常很多
much much fewer than the total number of
比总数少得多
objects have been allocated so therefore
对象已分配，因此
we don't have such a problem with to
我们没有这样的问题
long-john collections yep question
约翰·约翰长集合是问题
so the question is have you thought
所以问题是你有没有想过
about maybe using some kind of job
关于也许使用某种工作
annotations to provide hints yeah
提供提示的注释是的
you mean hints for a particular class
你的意思是关于某个特定班级的提示
yeah no we are not given that too much
是的，不，我们没有得到太多
thought and we I don't think there's
想到了，我们不认为有
that much we can use from such hints we
我们可以从这些提示中使用很多
are usually fine by fitting that out in
通常可以通过将其拟合
the JVM itself so no we are not thought
JVM本身，所以不，我们不认为
about it and but we might do but I don't
关于它，但我们可能会做，但我不知道
think there is too much we can value we
认为我们有太多我们可以珍视的东西
can get out from that I think there was
我可以从中脱身
another question maybe in the back yeah
另一个问题可能在后面
I do I foresee any other big
我会预见其他任何大事
improvements coming up to give one I
给我一个改进
actually do think that the ones who held
确实认为那些持有
up here on the sides might of course
当然可以在这边
differ between you and me but these are
你和我之间有所不同，但这些是
to me pretty big improvements and also
对我来说是很大的进步
the ones who are looking into rebuilding
那些正在寻求重建的人
remember SATs and improved ergonomics
记住SAT和改进的人体工程学
will also hopefully result in big
希望也会导致大
improvement so to me these are big to
对我来说这些进步很大
you I don't know
你我不知道
yeah yeah don't be doing any research
是的，没做任何研究
that we really revolutionize GC well I
我们真的彻底改变了GC
think about GC like 300 days a year so
想想一年大概300天这样的GC
yeah we do think a lot about it I don't
是的，我们确实考虑了很多
want to stand up here speculating what
想在这里站起来猜测
goes in and what comes knocking but yeah
进去，什么会敲，但是的
there's a lot of activity that we are
我们有很多活动
doing so hopefully that will result in
希望这样做会导致
some nice improvements it doesn't always
并非总是有一些不错的改进
do that unfortunately but a lot of the
不幸的是这样做，但是很多
time we can make some pretty good
时间我们可以做一些很好的
instruments and we will continue to do
仪器，我们将继续做
so yeah question
所以是的问题
yeah so the question is how much does
是的，所以问题是多少钱
the concurrent mark reduce the need for
同时标记减少了对
or the time for a full UC so G 1 doesn't
或者是完整UC的时间，所以G 1不会
useful you see in its normal operation
您在正常操作中看到的有用
as you saw on the slides even prefers to
正如您在幻灯片上看到的那样，甚至更喜欢
move between young collections and then
在年轻的收藏之间移动，然后
transition to young collections and
过渡到年轻的收藏和
concurrent mark and then transition into
并发标记，然后过渡到
mixed collections instead so it will
而是混合收藏，所以它将
collect the old radiance incrementally
逐渐收集旧的辐射
over a number of mixed collections and
多个混合馆藏
preferably don't have to do a full
最好不必做一个完整的
collection at all which means in a lot
收集意味着很多
lot smaller forced times compared to
与之相比，强制时间更短
full collections so hopefully we'll
完整的收藏，所以希望我们会
concurrent marking and the mixed
并发标记和混合
collections you can avoid felices
您可以避免狂欢的集合
completely and don't have to have them
完全不需要它们
at all
完全没有